Guide to the D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles archives, 1929-1995 and undated RL.00314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, ca. 1950-1986
  - Originals (Closed to Research)
    - Crest
      - Crest #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 368)
      - Crest #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 369)
      - Crest #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 370)
      - Crest #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 371)
        [Use Copy UC12 in collection]
      - Crest #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 372)
      - Crest #8 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 373)
      - Crest #9 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 374)
      - Crest #12 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 375)
        [Use Copy UC15 in collection]
      - Crest #13 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 376)
        [Use Copy UC16 in collection]
    - Vintage Television
      - E.S.P. (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 377)
      - Capt. Kelly (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 378)
      - Frontier Justice (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 379)
      - Mayberry R.F.D. (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 380)
      - The Loner (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 381)
      - Claudia (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 382)
      - Andy Williams (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 383)
      - Good Morning World (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 384)
      - Topper (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 385)
    - Post
      - Grape Nuts Flakes (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 386)
      - Cereal Advertising--Sandy Sulcer (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 387)
      - Honey Copmb Animatics (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 388)
      - Alpha Bits (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 389)
      - Sugar Crisp #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 390)
      - Sugar Crisp #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 391)
      - Sugar Crisp #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 392)
      - Sugar Crisp #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 393)
      - Sugar Crisp #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 394)
      - Sugar Crisp 76 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 395)
    - Discover Campaign (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 396)
    - Hardees (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 397)
    - Bravo/Glade (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 398)
    - Crest/Scope (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 399)
      [Use Copies UC15 (Crest), UC23(P&G), UC32 (Scope) in collection]
    - P & G--Multi-Reel (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 400)
    - Multi Brands (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 401)
    - Multi Brands (Dordelman) (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 402)
    - RUI--Multi Reel (RVI) (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 403)
    - Crest/Vicks (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 404)
      [Use Copy UC21 (Crest) in collection]
    - Maxwell House
      - Instant Maxwell House #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 405)
      - Instant Maxwell House #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 406)
      - Instant Maxwell House #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 407)
      - Instant Maxwell House #9 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 408)
      - Instant Maxwell House #10 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 409)
      - Instant Maxwell House #13 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 410)
    - Compiled 1 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 411)
    - Compiled 2 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 412)
    - Barbie (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 413)
    - AMF (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 414)
    - Vintage Television Shows
      - Run Buddy Run (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 415)
      - Green Acres (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 416)
      - Mayberry RFD--Andy's Baby # 31 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 417)
      - Alvin Show (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 418)
      - Edge of Night (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 419)
      - Ethel and Alpert (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 420)
      - The Night the Animals Talked (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 421)
      - Phil Silvers (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 422)
      - Hazel (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 423)
      - Danny Thomas, Jan. 14, 1957 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 424)
      - Yanks Are Coming I (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 425)
      - Yanks Are Coming II (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 426)
      - Lincoln--Trial By Fire (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 427)
      - Texaco Star Parade III (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 428)
      - Texaco Star Parade I (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 429)
      - Texaco Star Parade II (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 430)
    - Post
      - Oat Flakes, #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 431)
      - Miscellaneous #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 432)
      - Miscellaneous #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 433)
      - 40% Bran Hist #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 434)
      - Miscellaneous #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 435)
      - Miscellaneous #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 436)
      - Heart of Oats #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 437)
      - Misc #9 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 438)
      - Misc #10 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 439)
      - Misc #11 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 440)
    - Linus Post (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 441)
    - Flintstones (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 442)
    - Various B & B Spots (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 443)
    - Miscellaneous (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 444)
    - Miscellaneous--Non-DMB & B (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 445)
    - Linus--Faith For Today (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 446)
    - AMF (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 447)
    - Post Cereal (Old) (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 448)
    - Large Reels
      - Wondra (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 449)
      - Post (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 450)
      - Unknown (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 451)
      - Song of Norway (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 452)
      - Norwich #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 453)
      - Army (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 454)
    - Vintage Television
      - Lincoln--Trial By Fire (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 455)
      - Anything Goes (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 456)
      - The Honorable Sam Houston #1 (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 457)
      - The Honorable Sam Houston #2 (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 458)
      - Linus the Lionhearted (Box OV17, Reel 459)
      - Jack Benny Birthday Special (Box OV17, Reel 460)
      - High Hopes (Box OV17, Reel 461)
      - Jack Benny Birthday Special (Box OV17, Reel 462)
    - B & B New Business (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 463)
    - Mayberry RFD: Howard the Swinger (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 464)
    - Victory At Sea (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 465)
    - Sara Lee (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 466)
    - Maxim (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 467)
    - B & B Show (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 468)
    - B & B #23 (1600' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 469)
    - PS&D Symposium (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 470)
    - Alpha Bits #2 (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 471)
    - Gaines Burgers (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 472)
    - Gaines Burgers (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 473)
    - Gaines Burgers (large reel) (Box OV17, Reel 474)
    - Vintage Television
      - Linus the Lionhearted #4 (Box OV17, Reel 475)
      - Linus the Lionhearted #5 (Box OV17, Reel 476)
      - Linus the Lionhearted #6 (Box OV17, Reel 477)
    - Scope
      - Reel 478: Production Review No. 4 (Box AV1)
        [Use copy UC22 in collection]
      - Reel 479: Hysterical reel, Morning Breath (Box AV1)
        [Use copy UC23 in collection]
    - Vick's Cough Drops historical, 1929-1989, Reel 480 (Box AV1)
    - Bounce
      - Reel 481 (Box AV1)
      - Reel 482 (Box AV1)
    - Cool Whip
      - Reel 483 (Box AV1)
      - Reel 484 (Box AV1)
      - Reel 485 (Box AV1)
  - Preservation Masters (Not for Research Use)
    - Reel #1, Charmin Commercials (Box M1)
    - Reel #2, Charmin Commercials (Box M1)
    - Reel #3, Charmin Historical #3 (Box M1)
    - Reel #4, Charmin Historical #4 (Box M1)
    - Reel #5, Charmin Historical #5 (Box M1)
    - Reel #8, Charmin Historical #8 (Box M1)
    - Reel #6, Charmin Historical #6 (Box M2)
    - Reel #7, Charmin Historical #7 (Box M2)
    - Reel #9, Charmin Historical #9 (Box M2)
    - Reel #NA, P&G Production Review #4 (Box M3)
    - Reel #NA, Scope commercials--hysterical reel (Box M3)
    - Scope Reel 1, Film 284 (Box M3)
    - Scope Reel 2, Film 285 (Box M3)
    - Scope Reel 3, Film 286 (Box M3)
    - Scope Reel 4, Film 287 (Box M3)
    - Scope Reel 5, Film 288 (Box M3)
    - Scope Reel 6, Film 289 (Box M3)
    - Scope Reel 7, Film 290 (Box M3)
    - Pamp;G Reel 14, Film 399 (Box M3)
    - Scope Reel, Film 399 (Box M3)
    - Crest Tape 1, Reels 367, 237, 368 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 2, Reels 369, 370, 229 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 3, Reels 371, 372 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 4, Reels 373, 374, 136 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 5, Reels 168, 238 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 6, Reels 238 (continued), 375, 399, 232 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 7, Reels 376, 169 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 8, Reels 169 (continued), 170, 171 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 9, Reels 171 (continued), 172, 173 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 10, Reels 174, 175 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 11, Reels 139, 140 (Box M4)
    - Crest Tape 12, Reels 141, 142, 404 (Box M4)
  - Use Copies
    - UC1: Reel #1, Charmin Commercials. Reel 349. Format: VHS. Created: 2006 (Box U1)
    - UC2: Reel #2, Charmin Commercials. Reel 350. Format: VHS. Created: 2006 (Box U1)
    - UC3: Reel #3, Charmin Historical #3. Reel 351. Format: VHS. Created: 2006 (Box U1)
    - UC4: Reel #4, Charmin Historical #4. Reel 312. Format: VHS. Created: 2006 (Box U1)
    - UC5: Reel #5, Charmin Historical #5. Reel 352. Format: VHS. Created: 2006 (Box U1)
    - UC6: Reel #6, Charmin Historical #6. Reel 353. Format: VHS. Created: 2006 (Box U1)
    - UC7: Reel #7, Charmin Historical #7. Reel 354. Format: VHS. Created: 2006 (Box U1)
    - UC8: Reel #8, Charmin Historical #8. Reel 355. Format: VHS. Created: 2006 (Box U1)
    - UC9: Reel #9, Charmin Historical #9. Reel 356. Format: VHS. Created: 2006 (Box U1)
    - UC10: Crest Tape 1, Reels 367, 237, 368. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC11: Crest Tape 2, Reels 369, 370, 229. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC12: Crest Tape 3, Reels 371, 372. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC13: Crest Tape 4, Reels 373, 374, 136. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC14: Crest Tape 5, Reels 168, 238. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC15: Crest Tape 6, Reels 238 (continued), 375, 399, 232. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC16: Crest Tape 7, Reels 376, 169. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC17: Crest Tape 8, Reels 169 (continued), 170, 171. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC18: Crest Tape 9, Reels 171 (continued), 172, 173. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC19: Crest Tape 10, Reels 174, 175. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC20: Crest Tape 11, Reels 139, 140. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC21: Crest Tape 12, Reels 141, 142, 404. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC22: Reel #NA, P&G Production Review #4. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC23: Reel #NA, Scope commercials--hysterical reel. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC24: Scope Reel 1, Film 284. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC25: Scope Reel 2, Film 285. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC26: Scope Reel 3, Film 286. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC27: Scope Reel 4, Film 287. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC28: Scope Reel 5, Film 288. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC29: Scope Reel 6, Film 289. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC30: Scope Reel 7, Film 290. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC31: P&G Reel 14, Film 399. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)
    - UC32: Scope Reel, Film 399. Format: DVD. Created: 2007 (Box U2)